Guide to the Hanna House Collection SC0280
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Architectural drawings, 1936-1963
  - Addition to the residence of Professor & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer & WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 4, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_04; blueprints (reprographic copies); 29.5 x 41.5 inches
  - Addition to the residence of Professor & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer & WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 5, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_05; blueprints (reprographic copies); 29.5 x 41.5 inches
  - Addition and alterations to "Honeycomb house" for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, undated; sc0280_008; blueprints (reprographic copies); 34.5 x 42 inches
    Handwritten note on verso: "details of shelves and cabinets in living room"
  - Addition to the residence of Professor & Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer & WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 6, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_06; blueprints (reprographic copies); 29.5 x 41.5 inches
  - Addition and alterations to "Honeycomb house" for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, undated; sc0280_009; blueprints (reprographic copies); 36 x 42 inches
    Handwritten note on verso: "details shelves and cabinets in living room; organ and shelving; copy 2"
- Additional Architectural Drawings
  - Addition and alterations to "Honeycomb" House for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, CA, sc0280_001; 36 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Section A–A, Sash folding on track, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_002; 34.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size detail of clerestory windows, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_003; 31 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Furniture sheet No. 3, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_004; 33 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Details showing use of outside sash with the jamb, Sash sheet No. 2, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_005; 34 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Framing plan for pitched roofs, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_006; 36 x 35 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 1, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_01; 29.5 x 41.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 2, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_02; 29.5 x 41.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 3, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_03; 29.5 x 41.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 4, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_04; 29.5 x 41.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 5, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_05; 29.5 x 41.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 6, 1950-4-7; sc0280_007_06; 29.5 x 41.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition and alterations to "Honeycomb house" for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, sc0280_008; 34.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition and alterations to "Honeycomb house" for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, sc0280_009; 36 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, Revised Full Size details,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_010; 36 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, Revised Full Size details,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_011; 36 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Garden wall, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_012; 33.5 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Furniture Sheet No. 1, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_013; 33 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Furniture Sheet No. 2, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_014; 36 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Perforated Boards, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_015; 33 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Perforated Boards, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_016; 33 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Perforated Boards, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_017; 33 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Section A–A, Sash folding on track, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_018; 34 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Sash sheet No. 2, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_019; 32 x 26 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Sash sheet No. 2, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_020; 32.5 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Sash sheet No. 2, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_021; 34 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Sash sheet No. 2, Hanna House,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1937?; sc0280_022; 33 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul Hanna, Palo Alto, California, Frank Lloyd Wright, Revised Full Size details,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_023; 36 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size details of all typical jambs, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, 8,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_024; 33 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size details of all typical jambs, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, 8,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1937; sc0280_025; 33 x 41 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size details of all typical jambs, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, 8,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_026; 36 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size details of all typical jambs, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, 8,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_027; 33 x 41 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size details of all typical jambs, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, 8,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_028; 32.5 x 41 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - F.S. details for upper laboratory and bath, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1937; sc0280_029; 35.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Entrance lantern, Hanna house,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_030; 37.5 x 40.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size detail of clerestory windows, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1937; sc0280_031; 32 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Full size detail of clerestory windows, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_032; 30.5 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Framing plan for flat roofs and decks, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_033; 35 x 35.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Framing plan for flat roofs and decks, Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_034; 35 x 36 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 1, 1950-5-12; sc0280_035_01; 29.5 x 41. 5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 2, 1950-5-12; sc0280_035_02; 29.5 x 41. 5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 3, 1950-5-12; sc0280_035_03; 29.5 x 41. 5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 4, 1950-4-24; sc0280_035_04; 29.5 x 41. 5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 5, 1950-4-24; sc0280_035_05; 29.5 x 41. 5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 6, 1950-4-24; sc0280_035_06; 29.5 x 41. 5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 7, 1950-7-3; sc0280_035_07; 29.5 x 41. 5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Hanna Residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, 10, 1950-7-5; sc0280_035_08; 12 x 25.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Hanna Residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 12, 1950-7-18; sc0280_035_09; 29.5 x 28 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 14, 1950-10-12; sc0280_035_10; 20.5 x 30.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 14, 1950-10-12; sc0280_035_11; 20.5 x 30.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 1, 1950-5-12; sc0280_036_01; 30 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 2, 1950-5-12; sc0280_036_02; 30 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 3, 1950-4-24; sc0280_036_03; 29.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 4, 1950-4-24; sc0280_036_04; 30 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 5, 1950-4-24; sc0280_036_05; 30 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 6, 1950-4-24; sc0280_036_06; 30.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 7, 1950-5-23; sc0280_036_07; 30 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 8, 1950-7-24; sc0280_036_08; 30.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 9, 1950-8-9; sc0280_036_09; 11 x 18.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Hanna residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 10, 1950-7-5; sc0280_036_10; 12 x 25.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Hanna residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 11, 1950-7-10; sc0280_036_11; 29.5 x 28.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Hanna residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 12, 1950-7-18; sc0280_036_12; 29.5 x 28.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to Hanna residence, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Spencer Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 13, 1950-7-26; sc0280_036_13; 29.5 x 21.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 15, 1950-10-16; sc0280_036_14; 18 x 30 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 1, 1950-4-24; sc0280_037_01; 29.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 2, 1950-4-24; sc0280_037_02; 29.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 3, 1950-4-24; sc0280_037_03; 29.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 4, 1950-4-24; sc0280_037_04; 29.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 5, 1950-4-24; sc0280_037_05; 29.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to the residence of Professor Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, Frank Lloyd Wright architect, Eldridge T. Spencer WM Clement Ambrose Supervising Architects, 251 Kearny Street, San Francisco, 6, 1950-4-24; sc0280_037_06; 29.5 x 42 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Addition to House for Dr. Hanna, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_038; 29 x 28 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Workshop elevations, Addition to House for Dr. Hanna, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_039; 29.5 x 28 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Section Z-Z, For Dr. Hanna's House, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (Sept. 15, 1946) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1946-9-15; sc0280_040; 30 x 28 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Furniture for "Honeycomb" House, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (Sept. 20, 1946) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1946-9-25; sc0280_041; 29 x 28.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - For Dr. Hanna's House, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (Sept. 15, 1946) by Frank Lloyd Wright, 1946-9-15; sc0280_042; 29.5 x 28 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Completion of ventilator … Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_043; 13 x 17.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Completion of ventilator … Hanna House, Frank Lloyd Wright, Architect,initialed and dated (illegible) by Frank Lloyd Wright, sc0280_044; 13 x 17.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Mr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, Electrogas Unit; Electrogas Furnace Mfg. Co, 2575 Bayshore Boulevard, San Francisco, Engineering Department, 1937-2-12; sc0280_045; 17 x 24.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Mr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, Electrogas; Electrogas Furnace Mfg. Co, 2575 Bayshore Boulevard, San Francisco, Engineering Department, 1937-2-12; sc0280_046; 17 x 24.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Illumination Plan, Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #1, 1937-3-19; sc0280_047; 22 x 27.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Plan of Mat Tunnel, Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #2, 1937-3-19; sc0280_048; 22 x 27 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Plan of Mat Tunnel, Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #2, 1937-3-19; sc0280_049; 22.5 x 27.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #3, 1937-3-19; sc0280_050; 22.5 x 27.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #3, 1937-3-19; sc0280_051; 22.5 x 27.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #4, 1937-3-19; sc0280_052; 22.5 x 27 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #4, 1937-3-19; sc0280_053; 22 x 27 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #5, 1937-3-19; sc0280_054; 23 x 27.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Dwelling for Mr. and Mrs. Paul R. Hanna, Palo Alto, California, #5, 1937-3-19; sc0280_055; 23 x 27.5 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 1 of 3, 1951-12-28; sc0280_056_01; 12 x 39 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 2 of 3, 1951-12-28; sc0280_056_02; 12 x 39 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 3 of 3, 1951-12-28; sc0280_056_03; 12 x 39 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 1 of 2, 1951-10-15; sc0280_057_01; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 2 of 2, 1951-10-15; sc0280_057_02; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 1 of 2, 1951-10-15; sc0280_058_01; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 2 of 2, 1951-10-15; sc0280_058_02; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)
  - Barbeque shelter for Dr. Mrs. Paul Hanna, 737 Frenchman's Road, Stanford University, John C. Seward, Del. 1925 Pierce Street, San Francisco, 1 of 2, 1951-10-15; sc0280_059_01; 12 x 40 inches; 1 blueprints (reprographic copies)